Test square brackets removal
Multiple square brackets
Test round brackets removal
Multiple round brackets
Test uppercase followed by colon
Another uppercase test
Test word ending with colon
Another colon test
Test extra whitespace removal
Multiple spaces here
Test italic tag removal
Test bold tag removal
I'm testing lowercase L to I conversion
I'll also test I've and If and It's
defence testing US/UK spelling
colourful neighbour
Test single - dash conversion
No- space double dash-test
{}/\|#^*_<>
Testing special character removal
Test subtitle delay
This should be delayed by delay_ms
Test empty subtitle removal
Above subtitle should be removed