[MUSIC PLAYING] Test square brackets removal
[LAUGHTER] Multiple square brackets
(DOOR SLAMS) Test round brackets removal
(PHONE RINGS) Multiple round brackets
NARRATOR: Test uppercase followed by colon
JOHN: Another uppercase test
Character: Test word ending with colon
Sarah: Another colon test
♪ Testing music character removal ♪
♪ Second line with music ♪
Test   extra   whitespace   removal
Multiple    spaces    here
Test italic tag removal
Test bold tag removal
l'm testing lowercase L to I conversion
l'll also test l've and lf and lt's
defense testing US/UK spelling
colorful neighbor
Test single - dash conversion
No-- space double dash--test
[]{}()/\|#^*_<>
Testing special character removal
Test subtitle delay
This should be delayed by delay_ms
Test empty subtitle removal
Above subtitle should be removed